BRETT ITSUKI

Senior Full Stack Developer

SUMMARY

I am a senior web developer who specializes in SPA development using JavaScript. I'm especially expertized in React.js and Vue.js as well as having some experience with Angular. I also have rich experience in building backend APIs using Node.js and Python. I love learning and challenging.

EXPERIENCE

Senior Frontend Developer

05/2020 - 10/2022

Immersion

Remote

Company Description

- Developed many reusable components in React.js
- Implemented optimization for high performance
- Unit and E2E tests using Jest and Cypress
- · Developed frontend using SCSS and jQuery

Senior Full Stack Developer

11/2018 - 02/2020

NetCall

Remote

Company Description

- Developed customer service platforms using React.js and Typescript
- · Created reusable codes and styles
- · Developed frontend pages using Bootstrap and Tailwind CSS
- Developed back-end APIs using Express and Django and integrated third-party

Senior Frontend Developer

02/2018 - 08/2018

Itway

Remote

Company Description

- Developed frontend using Material UI and React-Bootstrap
- Worked with Figma designs
- Developed many mobile apps using React Native
- · Took part in developing projects using Next.js and Rest APIs

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science

2013 - 2017

Singapore University of Technology and Design

SKILLS

HTML / CSS ·

JavaScript / Typescript ·

React.js / Next.js · Angular ·

Vue.js / Nuxt.js · PHP / Laravel ·

Python / Django · Node.js / Express ·

MongoDB / PostgreSQL / MySQL ·

GraphQL / Apollo · AWS · Svelte ·

Git · Jira · Slack · Discord

LANGUAGES

English Proficient
O

Japanese Intermediate

HOBBIES

- Playing Football
- This is the state of the state
- ♥ Watching Movies
- Tistening to Music